bellesa.co 2019-05-11

# BELLESA – PRIVACY POLICY

                            BELLESA – PRIVACY POLICY
At Bellesa Enterprises Inc. (“Bellesa”), we are committed to maintaining the privacy and
security of your personal information, which is why Bellesa has created a respectful and
comprehensive Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy details how Bellesa collects, uses and
discloses personal information. This Privacy Policy applies to all transactions and activities
occurring through the Bellesa Website. When you use the Bellesa Website, you agree to the
terms set out in this Privacy Policy in effect at that time. Users must review this Privacy
Policy periodically as it is subject to changes/revision without notice.
This Privacy Policy will detail the following information:
What is Personal Information?
Information We Collect
Consent
Retention of Personal Information
Security Precautions
Agreement
Contact Us Regarding This Privacy Policy
What is Personal Information?
Bellesa does not track information that would render an individual personally identifiable, unless
that user willingly supplies that information to Bellesa.
Personal information is any information about a person including age, gender and location.
Bellesa may also track usage of/engagement with the Bellesa Website.
Bellesa does study group behaviour and demographics using analytics to help improve the
Website. Bellesa does not track or record information of individual users unless this information
is supplied directly by the user through our sign up form.
Information We Collect
Bellesa uses Personal Information to provide Bellesa Users with the best experience, and to tailor
the user experience to our user-base’s needs and preferences. Other uses of Personal Information
include, but are not limited to the following:
To update and verify your personal information that may already be in our database;
To respond to your inquiries and comments;
To register you for certain features on our Website;
To administer our programs;
To conduct surveys, contests and promotions;
To distribute, market, provide and inform you about Bellesa products and services by sending you
newsletters, promotional information, product samples, coupons, and/or e-mails and marketing
materials;

To help us understand your interests and develop new products and services that meets your
needs;
To comply with any laws or regulations and to cooperate with law enforcement inquiries; and
For any other purpose to which you consent.
We do not sell or redistribute personal information. Unless you consent in writing or unless
disclosure is required by law, we will not disclose your personal information to any third party
except as provided below:
To third party service providers with assurance that such third party service providers use the
personal information only as is required to perform the task they have been retained for, and agree
to follow policies compliant with privacy laws;
To comply with any legal requirements;
To enforce our privacy policy, or to protect your safety and security while visiting our website;
We may also disclose personal information to third parties in connection with a corporate re-
organization, merger or amalgamation, or the sale of all or substantially all of our assets, provided
that the personal information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this
Privacy Policy by the entity acquiring this information; or
To any other third parties, with your consent to such collection, use or disclosure.
You agree not to hold Bellesa liable for any misuse of your Personal Information by a third-party.
Consent
You may opt-out of being contacted and withdraw consent from having your personal information
used for marketing purposes or from having your personal information used for market research
purposes. Newsletters, promotional material and e-mails will detail how you may opt-out of being
contacted. Withdrawing consent or opting-out may in some instances result in your inability to
participate in certain programs, features or promotions.
You may also opt-out of receiving any communications from Bellesa.
Retention of Personal Information
We will only keep your personally identifiable information for as long as it is required for internal
business purposes and in order to satisfy various accounting and legal requirements. When we no
longer require information, we will take steps to ensure that it is destroyed, or that your
personally identifiable information is removed.
Security Precautions
Your Bellesa Profile is password-protected so that only you and authorized Bellesa employees
have access to your account information. In order to maintain this protection, do not give your
password to anyone. Bellesa staff will never proactively reach out to you and ask for any personal
account information, including your password. If you share a computer, you should sign out of
your Bellesa account and close the browser window before someone else logs on. This will help
protect your information entered on public terminals from disclosure to third parties.

Bellesa makes every effort to ensure that your information is secure on its system. Unfortunately,
no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, Bellesa
cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit. Any transmission made to or
through Bellesa is done at your own risks and perils. Bellesa expressly disclaims any liability that
may arise should any other individuals obtain the information you submit to or through the
Bellesa Website.
Bellesa has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the
information under our control. Your information may be transferred to and maintained on
computer networks which may be located outside of the state, province, country or other
governmental jurisdiction in which you reside, and the country or jurisdiction in which these
computer networks are located may not have privacy laws as protective as the laws in your
country or jurisdiction.
The Bellesa Application may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for
the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of
each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy
applies solely to information collected by the Bellesa Application.
Agreement
By using the Bellesa Website, you do hereby represent that you have read, understand and agree
to all terms of this Privacy Policy. Each time you use the Bellesa Website, you agree to all terms
set forth in this Privacy Policy.
Contact Us Regarding This Privacy Policy
You have the right to have a copy of the personal information you provide, and to correct or
update your personal information. Upon written request, we will inform you of the existence, use
and disclosure of your personal information and give you an opportunity to review your personal
information.
If you believe that we have not complied with this Privacy Policy or with respect to your personal
information, you may write the Privacy Officer at the following address:
contact@bellesa.co
